{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "1",
            "info": "Who was the legendary Benedictine monk who invented champagne?",
            "Answer": "Dom Perignon"
        },
        {
            "question": "2",
            "info": "Name the largest freshwater lake in the world.",
            "Answer": "Lake Superior"
        },
        {
            "question": "3",
            "info": "Where would you find the Sea of Tranquility?",
            "Answer": "The Moon"
        },
        {
            "question": "4",
            "info": "What is someone who shoes horses called?",
            "Answer": "A farrier"
        },
        {
            "question": "5",
            "info": "What item of clothing was named after its Scottish inventor?",
            "Answer": "A Mackintosh"
        },
        {
            "question": "6",
            "info": "What kind of weapon is a falchion?",
            "Answer": "A sword"
        },
        {
            "question": "7",
            "info": "Which word goes before vest, beans and quartet?",
            "Answer": "String"
        },
        {
            "question": "8",
            "info": "What is another word for lexicon?",
            "Answer": "Dictionary"
        },
        {
            "question": "9",
            "info": "Name the seventh planet from the sun.",
            "Answer": "Uranus"
        },
        {
            "question": "10",
            "info": "Who invented the rabies vaccination?",
            "Answer": "Louis Pasteur"
        },
        {
            "question": "11",
            "info": "True or false, Bill gates invented Apple",
            "Answer": "False"
        },
        {
            "question": "12",
            "info": "True or false, Steve Jobs invented Apple",
            "Answer": "True"
        },
        {
            "question": "13",
            "info": "Barrack Obama was the 3rd president",
            "Answer": "False"
        },
        {
            "question": "14",
            "info": "Will Arnett plays Gob in Arrested Development",
            "Answer": "True"
        },
        {
            "question": "15",
            "info": "Linus Torvalds is the maintainer of Linux",
            "Answer": "True"
        },
        {
            "question": "16",
            "info": "What year did the Paris Commune rise up?",
            "options": [
                "1870",
                "1871",
                "1872",
                "1873"
            ],
            "Answer": "1871"
        },
        {
            "question": "17",
            "info": "What year did the Soviet Union fall?",
            "options": [
                "1989",
                "1990",
                "1991",
                "1992"
            ],
            "Answer": "1991"
        },
        {
            "question": "18",
            "info": "What year did Civ 5 release?",
            "options": [
                "2007",
                "2008",
                "2009",
                "2010"
            ],
            "Answer": "2010"
        },
        {
            "question": "19",
            "info": "Which band is the best?",
            "options": [
                "Grateful Dead",
                "Wham!",
                "Marky Mark and the Funky Bunch",
                "Miami Sound Machine"
            ],
            "Answer": "Grateful Dead"
        },
        {
            "question": "20",
            "info": "Which Programming Language exists",
            "options": [
                "LISP",
                "Burnout Paradise!",
                "Gamethyon",
                "Teascript "
            ],
            "Answer": "LISP"
        }
    ]
}